<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	
	xmlns:georss="http://www.georss.org/georss"
	xmlns:geo="http://www.w3.org/2003/01/geo/wgs84_pos#"
	>

<channel>
	<title>wellness &#8211; Dailytweet</title>
	<atom:link href="/category/wellness/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>/</link>
	<description></description>
	<lastBuildDate>Wed, 06 Jan 2021 18:17:45 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=5.6</generator>

<image>
	<url>/wp-content/uploads/2020/12/cropped-android-chrome-512x512-1-1-32x32.png</url>
	<title>wellness &#8211; Dailytweet</title>
	<link>/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
<site xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">185396299</site>	<item>
		<title>What Happens To Your Body When You Eat Bananas Every Day</title>
		<link>/what-happens-to-your-body-when-you-eat-bananas-every-day/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[adminilyes1]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 10 Dec 2020 09:15:32 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[wellness]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/?p=627</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Bananas are one of those fruits that almost everyone loves eating, right from kids to the elderly. They taste so great that you can eat them when you crave something sweet, that too without feeling guilty. Though you may have been eating bananas regularly since childhood, are you aware of the many benefits it offers? [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>Bananas are one of those fruits that almost everyone loves eating, right from kids to the elderly. They taste so great that you can eat them when you crave something sweet, that too without feeling guilty. Though you may have been eating bananas regularly since childhood, are you aware of the many benefits it offers? If not, continue reading and learn what happens to your body when you eat bananas every day.</p>



<p><br>Many, many people all over the world suffer from asthma, including children. You may have tried many medications to heal the same but do you know eating banana regularly can help prevent asthma? A certain study has shown that children who ate the minimum one banana every day experienced much less wheezing compared to those who ate just a few bananas a month.</p>



<p>Your appetite will stay under control</p>



<p>Bananas are rich in fiber, and it helps normalize bowel movements, controls blood sugar, lowers cholesterol levels, and helps maintain a healthy weight. The fiber present in bananas slows down digestion and so you will feel full for long after you eat them. When you feel full you will eat less, and thus your appetite will stay under control and you will also lose weight.</p>


]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">627</post-id>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>The healing Qualities of Ginger tea</title>
		<link>/the-healing-qualities-of-ginger-tea/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[adminilyes1]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 09 Dec 2020 14:12:41 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[wellness]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/?p=620</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[A cup of ginger tea on a cold wintry morning can turn your day around. With its mildly pungent, fiery taste and deliciously exotic aroma, a warm cup of ginger tea is like a spa to your senses. Ginger tea is made from boiling the root of ginger in water for 10 to 15 minutes. [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>A cup of ginger tea on a cold wintry morning can turn your day around. With its mildly pungent, fiery taste and deliciously exotic aroma, a warm cup of ginger tea is like a spa to your senses. Ginger tea is made from boiling the root of ginger in water for 10 to 15 minutes. Sugar or honey can be added to flavor the beverage. Ginger is essentially the source of the plant Zingiber officinale. It is a herb but is often known as a spice due to its high taste. Ancient Indian and Chinese cultures have known the medicinal values of this herb for a long time. Of course, today, ginger tea is very popular in all parts of the world. Another tea known for its health benefits is hibiscus tea.&nbsp; Ginger tea has some significant benefits to general health. It has been known to improve blood circulation through the body thus maintaining a positive energy flowing through the body that keeps several kinds of diseases at bay. Chinese cultures have used ginger tea as a form of traditional medicine for over two thousand years and believed that its yang energy is what keeps the balance of elements in the body. The Indian Ayurveda to recommends the use of ginger tea as a cure and preventive measure for a variety of health problems.&nbsp; </p>



<p>Ginger tea regulates enzyme action in the body that improves the digestion of food particles. A cup of warm ginger tea every day before meals ensure proper digestion and efficient metabolism. Ginger tea also improves the appetite and keeps any gastric problems away. Another major health benefit of ginger tea is that it provides significant relief from motion sickness. For those who feel discomfort, nausea and dizziness during travel can get rid of such problems by consuming a cup of ginger tea before traveling. Ginger tea is a great stimulant for the senses and can provide instant relief from fatigue and giddiness. It also acts as an effective stress reliever.&nbsp; For centuries, ginger has been used as a home remedy for the cold and sore throat. </p>



<p></p>



<script async="" src="https://pagead2.googlesyndication.com/pagead/js/adsbygoogle.js"></script>
<!-- 336/280 SQUARE -->
<ins class="adsbygoogle" style="display:inline-block;width:336px;height:280px" data-ad-client="ca-pub-7408619455147859" data-ad-slot="5988273440"></ins>
<script>
     (adsbygoogle = window.adsbygoogle || []).push({});
</script>
<br>



<p>Ginger tea made with honey has an extremely soothing effect on the throat giving instant relief from a cough, pain, and congestion in the throat. Inhaling the steam from the ginger tea works miraculously on all kinds of respiratory problems. It soothes the lungs and provides relief from symptoms of asthma and congestion. It also acts as an effective expectorant and helps eliminate phlegm.&nbsp; Ginger tea also has unique benefits for anyone who has rheumatoid arthritis or any other kind of joint pains. Consuming ginger tea can help reduce pain and swelling. Alternatively, a ginger tea soak can give amazing relief from inflammation of the joints and reduce pain too. With so many benefits and its beautiful aromatic taste, ginger tea can well be a part of your daily regimen. Drink it every day and tap into the energy of the sun inherent in a cup of ginger tea.&nbsp;&nbsp; </p>



<p>Ginger Tea Has Many Soothing Qualities. Ginger tea has been used across the world, especially in the eastern countries like India and China for a long time. Ginger is a brown, fleshy, fibrous herb in root form. It has a pungent aroma and a strong, fiery taste with an astringent bite to it. Ginger tea is made by boiling fresh sliced or crushed ginger roots in water and simmering it for ten to fifteen minutes. A little bit of honey or lemon may be added for flavor and sweetness. Some people even like to add milk to theirs. The health benefits of ginger tea are many. Several types of research have proven that ginger consumption inhibits the deposition of cholesterol in the arteries. This significantly reduces the risk of heart disease and cardiovascular arrest. Apart from that, ginger has some very effective healing properties in a variety of ailments. Ginger is used in various traditional medicines, and ginger tea is the easiest and most delicious way of consuming ginger and achieving its maximum benefits. Hibiscus tea is also known for excellent health benefits.&nbsp; </p>



<p>A benefit that ginger tea has is that it helps in providing instant relief from motion sickness. A lot of people feel extremely nauseated and uncomfortable while traveling. Drinking a cup of ginger tea before you go not only helps you feel better but also helps you keep fresh throughout the journey. It has a soothing effect on the mind and keeps away feelings of nausea and dizziness. Ginger tea is also very beneficial in curing common respiratory problems like a cough, cold and sneezing. Ginger has great properties that help loosen the phlegm and expand the lungs. This aids in breathing and gives relief from any wheezing, or other breathing problems. </p>



<p>Ginger tea also offers respite from other problems associated with a cough and cold. It has an incredibly soothing effect on the sore throat. It also helps prevent allergies and sneezing.&nbsp; Ginger tea is great for your digestion too. Drinking a cup of green tea before or after meals helps release essential enzymes that aid the proper digestion of food thus eliminating any stomach disorders or digestive problems. Ginger tea also helps release gastric acids and improving the appetite. Ginger tea has been shown to have healing and anti-inflammatory effects on joints suffering from rheumatoid arthritis. It also relieves joint pain and helps relax the muscles. Apart from oral consumption, a soak made out of ginger tea can also be used in the affected areas to alleviate pain and swelling.&nbsp; </p>



<p>Ginger tea has some other important health benefits like reducing menstrual cramps and strengthening the immunity. It also does a great job at being an effective stress reliever, and its special enzymes and amino acids keep the blood flowing smoothly. This by improving the blood circulation in the body, ginger tea not only prevents heart diseases but also keeps your skin healthy and glowing.&nbsp; Drinking Ginger Green Tea Is Good For Health. At present, you can find a wide array of flavored teas in restaurants. Here, we are going to see the health benefits of drinking ginger tea in the daily diet. It is so easy to prepare from your home. </p>



<p>Drinking ginger green tea is good for health. This is a statement accepted by scientists all over the world. Increasing the appetite level of a user is one of the main health benefits of drinking this tea. Ginger tea, enriched with amazing health benefits can be made tastier by adding lime juice. It is found to be safe on people under all age groups. If you are in search of herbal tea to stimulate appetite level, then feel free to use this tea.&nbsp; Boosting the energy level of the user is another major advantage of adding ginger tea in the diet. Fatigue, the main health issue in today&#8217;s busy life can be well cured by using this tea. An anti-inflammatory is one among the highlighting properties of this tea. It treats inflammations and prevents health risks like arthritis and bone weakness. It is an apt choice for all who wish to prevent arthritis naturally.&nbsp; </p>



<p>As per studies, ginger is renowned for promoting the metabolic process of the body. Hence you can recommend this tea to all people who wish to enhance the metabolic process of the body. Lack of side effect is the main advantage of including this tea in the daily diet. When you compare other digestion promoting products with this tea, the latter one ensures complete safety of all users.&nbsp; Today, you can get different types of ginger products from the market in the form of extracts, capsules, and tablets. To ensure 100% safety, never hesitate to buy products from a trustworthy company. Constipation is one among the common health issue reported to indigestion. Lack of physical activity and excessive uses of processed and canned foods are some of the common causes reported for this health issue. You can minimize the risk of above-specified health issue by including ginger tea in the daily diet.&nbsp;</p>



<p> Ginger tea stimulates digestion and treats constipation naturally. If you feel any discomfort in the stomach, try to take this tea first. More than a dozen number of stomach ailments can be cured by using ginger tea. Promoting blood circulation throughout the body is found to be as the main health benefit of using this tea. Increased blood circulation in the body can minimize the risk of health issues like fatigue and headache. Hence it is an apt herbal remedy for all in search of a cure for poor blood circulation.&nbsp; Low immunity level in the body can lead the way too many health risks in life. How can we prevent low immunity level naturally? This question is quite common among people. Ginger green tea with amazing health benefits can answer the above question. It increases the immunity level of body and prevents health issues like cold and fever. Relieving stress is another main advantage of including this tea in the diet. It relaxes nerve cells and cures a wide range of health issues like depression and anxiety. Apart from the above-mentioned benefits, you can also ginger tea for menstrual discomforts and respiratory problems.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">620</post-id>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>10 Foods That Help Reduce Joint Pain</title>
		<link>/foods-help-reduce-joint-pain/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[adminilyes1]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 08 Oct 2020 09:21:05 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[wellness]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/?p=348</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[If you’ve got chronic knee or joint pain, you almost certainly feel the results all day, every day. you’ll have an inflammatory disease, bursitis, tendonitis, or associate injury, however of these conditions involve painful inflammation, and everyone will hurt whether or not you’re exploitation the joint or not. Extended periods of stillness cause even as [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>If you’ve got chronic knee or joint pain, you almost certainly feel the results all day, every day. you’ll have an inflammatory disease, bursitis, tendonitis, or associate injury, however of these conditions involve painful inflammation, and everyone will hurt whether or not you’re exploitation the joint or not. Extended periods of stillness cause even as abundant discomfort, if no more.</p>
<p>That’s as a result of your joints are designed to maneuver and don’t like being stationary. Moving them is really smart for healing, as long as you aren’t bearing an excessive amount of weight or creating identical repetitive motions that caused your injury within the 1st place. however are you able to bring yourself to induce up and move once you’re in most pain?</p>
<p>Medication from your doctor will facilitate, however you may be stunned by what quantity diet really plays a vicinity.</p>
<div id="welln-1194148255" class="welln-content_6">
<div id="taboola-mid-article-thumbnails-1x1" class=" trc_related_container trc_spotlight_widget trc_elastic trc_elastic_thumbnails-d " data-placement-name="Mid Article Thumbnails 1x1">
<div class="trc_rbox_container">
<div><span style="font-size: inherit;">Try intake additional of those eleven foods to alleviate that joint pain naturally. they’re all well-tried to support joint health, minimize pain, and facilitate get you moving once more.</span></div>
</div>
</div>
</div>
<div class="td_smart_list_6 td-2-columns ">
<div class="td-item">
<div class="td-number-and-title">&nbsp;</div>
<div class="td-number-and-title">
<h2><span class="td-sml-current-item-nr">1 &#8211; </span><span class="td-sml-current-item-title"><strong>Flaxseed</strong></span></h2>
</div>
<p><img class="td-animation-stack-type0-2 aligncenter" src="https://hhdresearch.org/wp-content/uploads/2018/12/linseed.jpg"></p>
<p>Eating linseed in a superb thanks to getting your omega-3s in no time flat. simply 2 tablespoons of ground linseed contain associate astonishing a hundred and fortieth of your daily price for omega-3 fatty acid fatty acids.</p>
<p>Studies show that regular consumption of flaxseeds will considerably decrease the production of pro-inflammatory compounds. this is often an excellent manner for vegetarians and vegans to induce their omega-3s during a plant-based type.</p>
<div class="td-number-and-title">
<h2><span class="td-sml-current-item-nr">2 &#8211; </span><span class="td-sml-current-item-title"><strong>Red Peppers</strong></span></h2>
</div>
<p><img class="aligncenter td-animation-stack-type0-2" src="https://hhdresearch.org/wp-content/uploads/2018/12/pexels-photo-452773.jpeg"></p>
<p>Not solely do sore joints like a discount in inflammation, however, they improve quite a bit after you will support the gristle, tendons, and ligaments that cushion them and keep them aligned.</p>
<p>Red peppers have plenty of water-soluble vitamins, that aids within the production of albuminoid. albuminoid holds along bone and muscle and offers structure to joints. alternative foods high in water-soluble vitamin embody grapefruit, oranges, tomato, and pineapple.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">348</post-id>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Middle Child Syndrome: Everything You Need to Know</title>
		<link>/middle-child-syndrome-everything-you-need-to-know/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[adminilyes1]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 02 Oct 2020 14:37:30 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[wellness]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/?p=339</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[It is not unusual for middle-borns to feel left out in the sibling shuffle. But is the middle child syndrome a real thing? Are all middle children resentful and bitter? Does being a middle child affect your personality? Should you be concerned about this condition? (Or for your kids developing the same?) Whether you are [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>It is not unusual for middle-borns to feel left out in the sibling shuffle. But is the middle child syndrome a real thing? Are all middle children resentful and bitter? Does being a middle child affect your personality? Should you be concerned about this condition? (Or for your kids developing the same?)</p>
<p>Whether you are a parent looking for tips to raise your younger ones well, or a middle child who’s curious to learn more about a ‘syndrome’ named especially after them, you have come to the right place.</p>
<p>In this guide on dealing with the middle child syndrome, we will help you find all the answers you need by uncovering the truth behind this ‘psychological condition.’</p>
<p>Let’s begin by first understanding what the syndrome entails in the first place.</p>
<h2>What Is Middle Child Syndrome?</h2>
<figure class="wp-block-image size-large"><img class="wp-image-339" src="https://web.archive.org/web/20200804024811im_/https://347077-1073788-1-raikfcquaxqncofqfm.stackpathdns.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/02/is-it-really-a-sundrome-1024x682.jpg" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" srcset="//web.archive.org/web/20200804024811im_/https://347077-1073788-1-raikfcquaxqncofqfm.stackpathdns.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/02/is-it-really-a-sundrome-1024x682.jpg 1024w, //web.archive.org/web/20200804024811im_/https://347077-1073788-1-raikfcquaxqncofqfm.stackpathdns.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/02/is-it-really-a-sundrome-300x200.jpg 300w, //web.archive.org/web/20200804024811im_/https://347077-1073788-1-raikfcquaxqncofqfm.stackpathdns.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/02/is-it-really-a-sundrome-768x512.jpg 768w, //web.archive.org/web/20200804024811im_/https://347077-1073788-1-raikfcquaxqncofqfm.stackpathdns.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/02/is-it-really-a-sundrome-1080x720.jpg 1080w, //web.archive.org/web/20200804024811im_/https://347077-1073788-1-raikfcquaxqncofqfm.stackpathdns.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/02/is-it-really-a-sundrome.jpg 1280w" alt="" /></figure>
<p>The middle child syndrome refers to the feeling of exclusion that is commonly experienced by most children who aren’t the eldest or the youngest in their group of siblings.  It is the belief that middle children often feel ignored, or at times, even completely neglected because of their birth order.</p>
<p>As the general belief goes, middle children tend to be resentful and bitter. They mostly have a negative outlook on life as they are plagued by feelings of unworthiness which ultimately characterizes into low self-esteem, and makes them isolate themselves from the outside world.</p>
<p>In extreme cases, middle child syndrome can also reflect on psychotic behavior in later years.</p>
<p>This condition was first explored by an Austrian psychiatrist, Alfred Adler, in 1964.</p>
<p>Adler, who worked closely with the renowned neurologist and the founder of psychoanalysis, Sigmund Freud, <a href="https://web.archive.org/web/20200804024811/https://www.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/pmc/articles/PMC3375868/">developed a theory</a> relating a person’s birth order with their personality development.</p>
<p>The theory suggested that a person’s rank among their siblings has a major influence on their mental wellbeing. It affects their ability to cope with stress and anxiety, as well as their problem-solving skills and psychological development later in life.</p>
<p>Many people agree that middle children are more susceptible to negative feelings than their siblings raised in the same environment. But the extent and severity of the middle child syndrome, as well as the likelihood of middle-born suffering from this condition, have long been debated over.</p>
<p>This brings us to the next question:</p>
<h2>Is the Middle Child Syndrome a Real Thing?</h2>
<p>Katrin Schumann, a certified psychologist, and researcher explore the concept in her book, <em>The Secret Power of the Middle Children</em>.</p>
<p>According to Schumann, middle child syndrome is not really a syndrome. Rather, it’s an ‘observation’ – i.e., the middle child syndrome is not something that you can catch or develop with the passage of time. It is more of a temporary behavior that dissipates on its own as the children grow older.</p>
<p>In other words, the symptoms of middle child syndrome do not necessarily depend on the birth order entirely. They have more to do with the family background and the manner in which the children are raised in the first place.</p>
<h2>Dealing with the Middle Child Syndrome</h2>
<p>You might have come across your fair share of relatives or acquaintances who believe that middle children tend to fare worse in life. Or perhaps what you read above resonated with you and you really do feel neglected, hurt, and, at times, even completely left out by your own family. You might be tired of being overshadowed by your siblings at various instances in life and feel like you never got the love and attention that you deserved from your parents.</p>
<p>If that’s the case, it’s important to remind yourself that as humans, we all make mistakes. Even if you feel like your parents hugely favor one child over the other, it is unlikely that they are doing it on purpose.</p>
<p>If it’s really too severe and you are having difficulty in dealing with the differences in behavior, it’s best to have a proper discussion. Rather than suffering in silence, let your family know about your concerns so that they can help solve it together.</p>
<p>Similarly, if you have a middle child of your own, reach out to them first. Have a friendly discussion to get to know if they feel left out. If you don’t want to be so straightforward, then it’s best that you take time out to make them feel special at least once in a while. Go out on a short trip, bake together, or do any other activity that brings you closer together. But remember not to overdo it because that can backfire and lead to exactly the opposite of what you’re trying to achieve.</p>
<h2>Concluding Note</h2>
<p>When it comes to dealing with middle child syndrome, the important thing to remember is that it is not a medical condition. Although it is common for middle children to feel neglected more than others in the family, the resulting ‘resentful’ behavior is not exclusive to middle-borns only. The eldest and youngest children in the family can also show rebellious behavior depending on their upbringing and the overall role that they play in the family.</p>
<p>Your personality might be slightly affected by your birth order. But it sure <em>isn’t</em> determined by it solely. So, regardless of what the world might say (or even how you might feel being dominated by your siblings at times), know that you are the master of your own fate. You can craft your personality exactly the way you want.</p>
<p>If you never get the spotlight to yourself, there’s no need to worry. Be your own light, and others shall seek you on their own!</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">339</post-id>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>one lemon a day will keep the Dr away</title>
		<link>/one-lemon-a-day-will-keep-the-kidney-stones-away/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[adminilyes1]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 26 Sep 2020 12:23:38 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[wellness]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/?p=316</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[the benefit of lemons and a lemon a day will keep the kidney stones away let me tell you why because some people are trying to get healthy nowadays so they&#8217;re adding more kale to the diet more spinach or leafy greens and then they may end up with a kidney stone why because some [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>the benefit of lemons and a lemon a day will keep the kidney stones away let me tell you why because some people are trying to get healthy nowadays so they&#8217;re adding more kale to the diet more spinach or leafy greens and then they may end up with a kidney stone why because some of those foods are high in oxalates and what&#8217;s an excellent an oxalate is a certain chemical that can combine with calcium in your body and possibly develop kidney stones</p>
<p>now I had a kidney stew a long time ago and it is the worst thing on the planet I was you I just lost my sense of humor really fast but the point is that what does what dissolves oxalate stones this citric acid in the lemon okay so I make sure I have at least one lemon every single day and I put it my water or I&#8217;ll take the lemon juice I like the organic I like the Italian lemon juice is volcano lemon juice if you can find it in healthy store or just get organic lemon juice okay don&#8217;t get the regular stuff get the organic stuff and do maybe like two ounces of lemon juice in the water every day and you will not have to worry about kidney stones it really works</p>
<p>and you can even put it in that kale shake that you drink as well the other thing is that if you take a real lemon make sure that you get the organic lemons because there&#8217;s a lot of pesticides on them or if you you know if you don&#8217;t get organic lemon and you get a regular one just make sure you wash it really really well before you start cutting it because sometimes people even at a restaurant they cut up the lemon you don&#8217;t you&#8217;re just getting pesticides you put it right on the water you don&#8217;t want to do that okay so it&#8217;s a real simple tip go ahead and start adding at least one lemon to your diet every single day</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">316</post-id>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>These Are The 10 Best Brain-Boosting Foods Out There ..</title>
		<link>/these-are-the-20-best-brain-boosting-foods-out-there/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[adminilyes1]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 08 Sep 2020 09:59:49 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[wellness]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/?p=239</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[By this stage, we all probably know just how important our diet is to how well we function on a day to day basis. If you don’t, then take it from us: it’s important! Aside from having a huge effect on our bodies and our physical health, food can also have a big impact on [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>By this stage, we all probably know just how important our diet is to how well we function on a day to day basis. If you don’t, then take it from us: it’s important! Aside from having a huge effect on our bodies and our physical health, food can also have a big impact on our mental health as well. Some foods that we ate can make us mentally foggy and out of balance, others can give us that extra boost we need to succeed. It’s that second category of foods that we’re going to walk you through today! With no further ado, here are the 20 best brain-boosting foods out there.</p>



<p class="has-vivid-cyan-blue-color has-text-color has-large-font-size"><strong>Sprulina </strong></p>



<p>It’s an extremely healthy nutritional supplement with not one single man-made chemical in it.&nbsp;It’s also very easy to digest, and gives you a&nbsp;<strong>feeling of fullness</strong>&nbsp;for a rather long time.</p>



<p>Millions of people all over the world use spirulina as a dietary supplement, following the recommendations of the&nbsp;<strong>United Nations</strong>&nbsp;(UN) and the&nbsp;<strong>World Health Organization</strong></p>



<p class="has-medium-font-size"><strong>it improves your memory </strong></p>



<p>Eating spirulina can help improve your memory capacity.&nbsp;This is because it protects your cognitive systems and&nbsp;<strong>stimulates your brain and nervous system</strong>.&nbsp;It’s also great for your general well-being. Both of those things can help keep your mood stable&nbsp;and lower your stress.</p>



<p class="has-medium-font-size"><strong>It gives you energy</strong> &amp; relaxes your brain</p>



<p>Eating some every day can&nbsp;<strong>make you feel less tired</strong>.&nbsp;That’s why it’s good for both athletic people&nbsp;and people who don’t exercise much but are trying to start. It can help everyone push themselves and make their training much more efficient and productive.</p>



<p>One of the main ingredients in spirulina is tryptophan, which synthesizes other proteins and balances out your nervous system. Tryptophan is an amino acid that’s also the key to your body’s production of&nbsp;<a href="https://exploringyourmind.com/the-pleasure-hormone-serotonin-and-how-it-affects-your-body/">serotonin</a>, the happiness hormone. Because it’s necessary for serotonin, it helps&nbsp;<strong>regulate mood, stress, and appetite.</strong></p>



<p>You also need tryptophan to produce&nbsp;<a href="https://exploringyourmind.com/melatonin-the-sleep-and-youthfulness-hormone/">melatonin</a>&nbsp;in your body. Melatonin is the main hormone for regulating your sleep cycles, so it’s an important part of&nbsp;<strong>getting good sleep.</strong></p>



<p class="has-vivid-cyan-blue-color has-text-color has-large-font-size"><strong>Dark chocolate</strong></p>



<p>Are you craving a luscious way to keep your brain at its best? Reach for some dark chocolate. A study published in the&nbsp;<em>Neuroscience &amp; Biobehavioral Reviews&nbsp;</em>journal found that dark chocolate is a superfood due to its high levels of flavanols. These are special compounds that have been shown to help improve blood flow to the brain, which can increase cognitive function and memory. Another reason to feel good about enjoying dark chocolate is because it has an abundance of polyphenols. These are unique phytochemicals that have been shown to help reduce depression and anxiety. Just remember to choose dark chocolate with at least 70% cacao and try to indulge in no more than two squares a day. So now when you have some dark chocolate, remember that you’re also giving your brain a sweet treat.</p>



<p class="has-vivid-cyan-blue-color has-text-color has-large-font-size">Beets make you smart &amp; young</p>



<p>The humble beet has been found to boost your gray matter during exercise, thanks to its high levels of oxygen-enhancing nitrates, researchers at Wake Forest University found. In a study, 26 middle-aged men and women with high blood pressure drank either beet juice or a placebo before exercising — and the ones who got the beets, had much higher levels of nitric oxide, which increases blood and oxygen flow in the body.</p>



<p>&#8220;Nitric oxide is a really powerful molecule,&#8221; said&nbsp;<a href="https://www.eurekalert.org/pub_releases/2017-04/wfu-wbj041817.php">study coauthor W. Jack Rejeski.</a>&nbsp;&#8220;It goes to the areas of the body which are hypoxic, or needing oxygen, and the brain is a heavy feeder of oxygen in your body.&#8221;</p>



<p class="has-vivid-cyan-blue-color has-text-color has-large-font-size">Walnuts</p>



<p>Walnuts like other dry fruit are extremely nutritional they are rich in omega 3 vitamins B6-B1-B2-B3 and B5 protein; fats; dietary fiber and amino acids, that&#8217;s why they are so excellent for our body and brain for brain health it&#8217;s time to go nuts&#8211;walnuts, that offers numerous brain health benefits to start they are packed with omega3 fatty acids that help protect the fatty portion of your brain and quell brain inflammation too it can imrove signals between brain cells, increase the generation of brain and nerve cells walnuts are suck powerful brain protectors that new research published in the Journal of Alzheimer&#8217;s Disease found that eating only 1 to 2 ounces of the researchers indicated that the nuts are a preventive remedy against Alzheimer&#8217;s disease</p>



<p class="has-vivid-cyan-blue-color has-text-color has-large-font-size"><strong> Coconut Oil</strong></p>



<p>the human brain requires a continuous source of energy to make it function correctly. as soon as this energy steam gets interrupted neurons in the brain start to dir out. the immediate effect of this condition are headache, exhaustion and brain fog. but in the long run, a lack of energy supply to the brain leads to permanent degeneration of the human brain recent research has indicated towards coconut oils ability to provide the brain with a clean fuel source that takes care of all short term and long term effects of energy deprivation on the brain.</p>



<p class="has-vivid-cyan-blue-color has-text-color has-large-font-size"><strong> Black Beans</strong></p>



<p>Aside from being a cheap food that goes with all kinds of different dishes, black beans also have some unexpected benefits for your brain. As it turns out, black beans come packed with plenty of folate and magnesium, both of which can help reverse the effects of Alzheimer’s disease.</p>



<p class="has-vivid-cyan-blue-color has-text-color has-large-font-size"><strong> Spinach</strong></p>



<p>spinach is a storehouse of essential nutrients such as proteins, mineral, and vitamins being high in potassium; spinach is exceptionally good for the brain potassium helps maintain the electrical conductivity of the brain this helps produce lightning-fast signals between neurons, which, in turn, improves thinking and recall capacity. the antioxidant content in spinach protects the brain cells from oxidative damage this leafy the green vegetable is also loaded with nutrient including folate, magnesium, and vitamins E and K which help prevent dementia in diseases such as Alzheimer&#8217;s</p>



<p class="has-vivid-cyan-blue-color has-text-color has-large-font-size"><strong> Pumpkin Seeds</strong></p>



<p>pumpkin seeds, also known as peptis, nestle in the core of the pumpkin encased in a white-yellow husk, these super seeds contain a number of minerals such as zinc magnesium manganese iron copper and phos-phurs along with proteins monounsaturated fat, and the omega 3 and omega 6 fatty acids &#8211; all of the wich aid the brain in a different way they also contain the amino acid glutamate which helps the brain produce the antianxiety chemical gaba. pumpkin seeds help improve memory and focus</p>



<p class="has-vivid-cyan-blue-color has-text-color has-large-font-size"><strong>Asparagus</strong></p>



<p>Though it should come as no surprise that green vegetables are goof for you, it’s worth mentioning asparagus on this list as well. Like the above, it also has important prebiotic fibers that help strengthen the gut. As an added bonus, it also has plenty of folate and other trace nutrients that help fight against inflammation. All good things!</p>



<p class="has-vivid-cyan-blue-color has-text-color has-large-font-size"><strong> Almonds</strong></p>



<p>almonds are one of the top brain foods, providing choline, which feeds neurons an empty cough drop or mint tin is the perfect dose of roasted almonds to nosh on in the classroom eating almonds helps you to take a break and refuel the brain at the same time teachers need snack time too! hit the pause button and recharge your brain with almonds for amygdala</p>



<p>&nbsp;</p>



<h2></h2>



<p>&nbsp;</p>



<p>&nbsp;</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">239</post-id>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>7 Foods to Eat and Have Healthy Diet</title>
		<link>/7-foods-to-eat-and-have-healthy-diet/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[adminilyes1]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 27 Aug 2020 08:14:34 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[wellness]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/?p=149</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Many of us understand that eating in moderation contributes very much to our healthy lifestyle. In that case, for most of us, that, unfortunately, means eating less food. While that sound advice in regards to a large number of our best foods brownies, for instance, Honestly . The restrictive way of this philosophy conflicts with [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Many of us understand that eating in moderation contributes very much to our healthy lifestyle. In that case, for most of us, that, unfortunately, means eating less food.</p>
<p>While that sound advice in regards to a large number of our best foods brownies, for instance, Honestly . The restrictive way of this philosophy conflicts with our rebellious nature making our healthy eating somewhat less appealing.</p>
<p>That is the reason behind we are going to take different strategy and concentrate on foods we ought to all be eating a greater amount. That is right and sounds great; we know it makes that entire healthy eating feel somewhat more fun. We have gathered some of healthy foods that you can more of them in dairy services and have no effect on your health. Here are best foods you can eat.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">149</post-id>	</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
