<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	
	xmlns:georss="http://www.georss.org/georss"
	xmlns:geo="http://www.w3.org/2003/01/geo/wgs84_pos#"
	>

<channel>
	<title>LIFE &#8211; Dailytweet</title>
	<atom:link href="/category/life/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>/</link>
	<description></description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sat, 09 Jan 2021 12:57:26 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=5.6</generator>

<image>
	<url>/wp-content/uploads/2020/12/cropped-android-chrome-512x512-1-1-32x32.png</url>
	<title>LIFE &#8211; Dailytweet</title>
	<link>/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
<site xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">185396299</site>	<item>
		<title>Little Changes You Can Make to Be the Happiest Person Alive Today</title>
		<link>/little-changes-you-can-make-to-be-the-happiest-person-alive-today/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[adminilyes1]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 30 Nov 2020 12:08:03 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[LIFE]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/?p=486</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Secrets to living a happier lifeWouldn’t you want to learn how to be happier in life? It’s a question that we all ask ourselves at some point in our life. But you cannot successfully answer it, let alone strive towards achieving happiness in life unless you realize this one basic thing: Happiness is not a [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p class="has-vce-cat-0-color has-text-color">Secrets to living a happier life<br>Wouldn’t you want to learn how to be happier in life?</p>



<p>It’s a question that we all ask ourselves at some point in our life. But you cannot successfully answer it, let alone strive towards achieving happiness in life unless you realize this one basic thing:</p>



<p>Happiness is not a station you arrive at, but a manner of traveling.</p>



<p>Happiness is not a destination – it’s a journey.</p>



<p>Most of us tend to think of happiness as a result. But in reality, happiness is also a driver to achieve more.</p>



<p>Unlike pleasure, which is generally a short-lived feeling of joy that comes from indulging in certain activities or through the fulfillment of a certain goal, happiness is more long-lasting. It is a stable and more permanent state of mind that helps you maintain a positive outlook on life regardless of what your current circumstances might be.</p>



<p>But what is the secret to living a happier life?</p>



<p>If you ask those who are already living the life that they have always dreamed of, most of them are likely to say something along the lines of making ‘small changes’ in your lifestyle.</p>



<p>Is it true? Can small changes make a big difference in determining how happy you are in life?</p>



<p>There’s only one way to find out.</p>



<p>Try to incorporate as many of the following habits as you can into your lifestyle:</p>



<p>1. Make a Pledge to Be Happy</p>



<p>Whatever the mind says, the body follows. So, consciously tune your mind to being happy and you will actually feel happy all the time.</p>



<p>Write motivational messages or well wishes for your own self and post them at different places throughout the home or on your office desk where you can see them multiple times throughout the day. This can be a simple one-liner such as ‘today is a good day to be happy.’</p>



<p>Or you can also frame a picture of your best moment(s) in life and place it by your bedside. When you begin the day by being reminded of a happy day, you will look forward to turning the following day into a memorable one as well.</p>



<p>2. Let Go of the Past</p>



<p>If you often find yourself sulking over the past events in your life, you are obviously burning your own happiness for no apparent gain. Learn to let go of the past, and stop feeling remorseful. Remember- no one makes mistakes deliberately. In fact, we only call them mistakes in hindsight.</p>



<p>Remind yourself that you are an incredible person with the power to achieve anything and everything that you set your mind to.</p>



<p>Repeat this affirmation until it actually sinks in.</p>



<p>And to really let go of the past for good, try to face it once and for all. Pour your heart out and pen down all those anguished thoughts. Then burn the paper, bury it underground, or simply toss in the bin – but go to bed that night knowing that it’s all out of your system.</p>


]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">486</post-id>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>five simple Steps to Change Your Life (2021)</title>
		<link>/five-simple-steps-to-change-your-life/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[adminilyes1]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 09 Nov 2020 15:11:52 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[LIFE]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/?p=398</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Dr. Joe Dispenza, is an international lecturer, researcher, corporate consultant, author, and educator who has been invited to speak in more than 32 countries on five continents. As a lecturer and educator, he is driven by the conviction that each of us has the potential for greatness and unlimited abilities. In his easy-to-understand, encouraging, and [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p><strong>Dr. Joe Dispenza, is an international lecturer, researcher, corporate consultant, author, and educator who has been invited to speak in more than 32 countries on five continents. As a lecturer and educator, he is driven by the conviction that each of us has the potential for greatness and unlimited abilities. In his easy-to-understand, encouraging, and compassionate style, he has educated thousands of people, detailing how they can rewire their brains and recondition their bodies to make lasting changes.</strong></p>



<h4 style="font-size:14px"><span style="font-weight: 400; color: #333333;">I want to take a moment and teach you some basic tools to begin to change your life when you invest in yourself you invest in your future number one take some time out of your busy lives to disconnect from your world shut your cell phone off turn the TV off power down your computer sit your body down for a few minutes and close your eyes&nbsp;</span></h4>



<h4 style="font-size:14px"><span style="font-weight: 400; color: #333333;">2 &#8211; take some breaths and Center yourself when you Center your attention into the present moment you have more energy to create one when your mind wanders to the predictable future of the familiar past that&#8217;s normal just become aware of it keep working on settling yourself back down into the present moment when you&#8217;re in the present moment you&#8217;re the most creative </span></h4>



<h4 style="font-size:14px"><span style="font-weight: 400; color: #333333;">3 &#8211; ask yourself can I be defined by a vision of the future instead of memories of the past what do I want in my life and take the time to answer the question as you begin to contemplate and think about the answer to the question you&#8217;re changing your brain when you make your brain fire in new sequences and new patterns in new combinations that&#8217;s the beginning steps of changing your mind next decide on the emotions you feel when you begin to create that future and teach your body emotionally but that future is going to feel like and don&#8217;t get up until you begin to feel those emotions</span></h4>



<h6 style="font-size:14px">&nbsp;</h6>



<h4 style="font-size:14px"><span style="font-weight: 400; color: #333333;">Next Step number for rehearsing in your mind who you&#8217;re going to be when you open your eyes the things you have to do the choices you have to take steps you have to take review them over and over again</span></h4>



<h4 style="font-size:14px"><span style="font-weight: 400; color: #333333;">5 &#8211; you can go to the Future holding on to the biology of your past decide what thoughts do bring to your future write them down thoughts like I can&#8217;t it&#8217;s too hard I&#8217;ll never change I&#8217;ll start tomorrow what&#8217;s wrong with me someone else&#8217;s fault decide what behaviors are actions are unconscious habits you have to change how do you talk to you complain the blame you make excuses you feel sorry for yourself just become so conscious of their behaviors that you&#8217;ll never go unconscious again </span></h4>



<h4 class="has-normal-font-size">lastly,<span style="font-weight: 400; color: #333333;"> you have to decide what emotions no longer belong in your future that means if you want to be wealthy you can take black if you want to be healthy you can take insecurities for fear you got to begin to condition your body to a new mind if you do this every single day your personality creates your personal reality and your personality is made up of how you think how you act and how you feel change any one of those things and you change your life and begin to measure the effects of you would cost give it a shot</span></h4>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">398</post-id>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>6 Tips to feel Happier : Living a Free and Happy Life</title>
		<link>/6-tips-to-feel-happier-living-a-free-and-happy-life/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[adminilyes1]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 04 Nov 2020 11:24:59 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[LIFE]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/?p=390</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[6 Tips Backed by Scientific Research for happy life Achieving real happiness is easy as 1, 2, 3 once you understand the true essence of this word. Discover the secrets of attaining happiness in this detailed guide covering the top tips for living a good life. Are you aware of the ‘Happiness Myth’? You might [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>6 Tips Backed by Scientific Research for happy life<br />
Achieving real happiness is easy as 1, 2, 3 once you understand the true essence of this word. Discover the secrets of attaining happiness in this detailed guide covering the top tips for living a good life.</p>
<p>Are you aware of the ‘Happiness Myth’?</p>
<p>You might not know it directly. But the ironic part is that like millions of other people in the pursuit of happiness, you too probably believe it to be true. In fact, there’s a high chance that you are living the myth already.</p>
<p>But what exactly is the happiness myth? How can you ensure that you don’t fall victim to the false beliefs of attaining happiness? And how can you achieve real, long-lasting happiness anyway?</p>
<p>In the following article, we will help you find the answers to everything you need to know about achieving true happiness.</p>
<p>This comprehensive guide discusses scientifically-backed tips for living a good life and simultaneously provides valuable insights into what prevents people from living the life they dream about.</p>
<p>If you are ready to turn your life around for the better, take a deep breath – it’s time to get started!</p>
<p>Let’s begin by first understanding what being happier in life entails in the first place.</p>
<p>Debunking the Happiness Myth<br />
The widely held (and incorrect) notion about happiness is that it comes through the fulfillment of your goals.</p>
<p>We are usually taught from a very young age that if we work hard and become successful, happiness will automatically follow.</p>
<p>Modern philosopher, psychology professor, and commentator, Jennifer M. Hecht, explains the misconception about happiness in her best-selling book The Happiness Myth: Why What We Think Is Right Is Wrong.</p>
<p>Hecht reveals how the modern economy is designed to thrive on people’s attempts to be happy in life. It misrepresents happiness because happiness simply isn’t good for business.</p>
<p>If you are happy with what you have, why would you need more?</p>
<p>Shawn Achor, known as one of the leading experts on the power of positive psychology, further highlights this concept in his research-based book, The Happiness Advantage.</p>
<p>Survey results show that a majority of Americans find it harder to enjoy free time than to stay busy at work.</p>
<p>This is because they are blindly following the preconceived notion that once they are successful, they will be happy.</p>
<p>If you think that you will achieve happiness once when finally land your dream job, marry the love of your life, buy your own house and so on, stop right here! And think again.</p>
<p>Happiness never comes from achieving something or someone. It is a part of your essence. It is something that comes from within.</p>
<p>As Khalil Gibran artfully said:</p>
<p>“Happiness is a myth we seek,</p>
<p>If manifested surely irks;</p>
<p>Like river speeding to the plain,</p>
<p>On its arrival slows and murks.”</p>
<p>This illustrates that while you might enjoy a sense of wellbeing as you aspire and push forth towards achieving a goal, the fact is that the feeling eludes you when you finally do meet your target. You cool off and start longing for other distant goals.</p>
<p>And this cycle never ends. So, to be happy in the real sense, you need to break free from this cycle and adopt healthy habits that not just rectify this general attitude, but also help you live a happier, more fulfilling life.</p>
<p>Tips for Living a Good Life<br />
Being happy in life is not as challenging as you might initially perceive it to be.</p>
<p>The following are some simple and easy-to-follow tips for living a good life that will raise your happiness level and help you stay cheerful even when things don’t go according to plan.</p>
<p>1. Eat Well<br />
If you are thinking, ‘wait, what do my eating habits have to do anything with how I feel?’ you aren’t alone. Many people are completely unaware of the effect of food on mental health.</p>
<p>Good food and good mood go together hand in hand.</p>
<p>When you eat unhealthy food items, you might gain short-term pleasure, but at the back of your mind, you yourself are aware of the long-term damage it can cause.</p>
<p>On the other hand, adopting healthy eating habits improves your sense of wellbeing and encourages you to take better care of yourself.</p>
<p>Research shows that eating fresh fruits and vegetables serves as an instant mood booster because it has a therapeutic effect. Various naturally found compounds in fruits and veggies have antidepressant properties and are essential for better mental health.</p>
<p>Replace your store-bought snacks with homemade salads, smoothies, and other nutritious goodies and you will soon notice the benefits on your body as well as the soul.</p>
<p>You need to remember, you are what you eat. So, eat your way to happiness!</p>
<p>2. Disconnect From the Online World<br />
All it takes is the click of a button – and social media sites help you get in touch with distant friends and family members anywhere and at any time.</p>
<p>But ironically, while social media has brought distant people together, it has also increased the distances between people at the same time.</p>
<p>Social media sites keep scrolling through the feeds idly for hours. You check your phone once every few minutes for a new message or update. You are constantly distracted by the buzz of notifications. And of course, eagerly anticipate getting the maximum number of likes on the post you just shared.</p>
<p>When you are so fixated on such things, your life tends to become more complicated than your Facebook relationship status.</p>
<p>Various studies reveal how excessive use of social media and an increased feeling of stress and anxiety have a positive correlation.</p>
<p>Recall the last time you saw a picture of your friend cruising at the Bahamas and wished you were there rather than sulking at your office desk.</p>
<p>If you preoccupy yourself with what others are doing in their lives and sharing on social media, you lose focus on your own goals.</p>
<p>You end up comparing yourself with others and this ultimately leads to low self-esteem, depression, inattention, and hyperactivity.</p>
<p>Put simply, one of the top tips for living a good life full of happiness is to limit your use of social media.</p>
<p>Don’t worry about being out of touch. Your true friends would know how to contact you nonetheless.</p>
<p>On a side note, when you come across something on social media that makes you feel like your life is less than perfect; remind yourself that no one posts their failures online.</p>
<p>3. Log In to the Real World<br />
When you have successfully learned how to disconnect yourself from social media, consider logging in to the real world to utilize the free time in the best possible manner.</p>
<p>And the best way to do so is to go out for a walk whenever you get time.</p>
<p>Be it a cold winter morning or a warm sunny day, let nothing stop you from taking a stroll outdoors.</p>
<p>Incorporating brisk walk or jogging into your daily routine not only brings in multiple health benefits but also plays an important role in determining your happiness level.</p>
<p>Research has shown that traveling to work on foot can actually boost productivity as it aids concentration and keeps you energized for the rest of the day.</p>
<p>If your workplace is relatively too far to walk, consider cycling to the office instead. This helps you connect with nature as you stay more attentive to your surroundings. Plus, the smell of the air and the rush of wind that you feel when out under the open sky can alleviate stress and increase mindfulness.</p>
<p>4. Use the Power of Kawaii<br />
This step may sound weird to many people, but like all other tips for living a good life covered in this article, this one is also backed by scientific research.</p>
<p>Kawaii is a Japanese word that literally means cute.</p>
<p>According to Japanese researchers, looking at pictures of cute animals like kittens and puppies or surrounding yourself with similar cute items such as stuff toys has the potential to make you feel happier.</p>
<p>This makes sense if you take a deeper look at the Japanese culture. You will come across many images of characters like Hello Kitty that evoke cute and childlike vibes. This is because these things produce positive feelings that help you increase focus and boost productivity. When you perform better, you feel better and this, in turn, improves your overall wellbeing.</p>
<p>It might not be something that your boss would be willing to hear. But using the power of kawaii is surely worth a try.</p>
<p>Don’t fret about what others might think and consider bringing a cute teddy bear at work. If that’s too mainstream for you, you can at least place a few adorable items on your desk instead. This can include a desk calendar with cute images of babies or any other stationery item that doesn’t scream ‘professionalism.’</p>
<p>5. Get Proper Night Sleep<br />
Maintaining a proper sleep-wake schedule is highly important if you want to improve the quality of your life.</p>
<p>A lack of sleep not only makes you feel lethargic all day long but also reflects poorly on your mood. You are more susceptible to feeling sad and in most cases, angry for no apparent reason. Small things are more likely to irritate you.</p>
<p>When you are tired, minor problems seem like a huge hurdle and you might end up making a mountain out of a molehill. But that’s not all.</p>
<p>Scientists believe that getting a proper night’s sleep is essential because it helps you fight daily stressors and thus, stay in a cheery mood.</p>
<p>The Rapid Eye Movement (REM) sleep stage occurs just before you are about to wake up. During this time your brain is more active and processing things at an incredibly fast pace without you having the slightest hint.</p>
<p>When you force yourself to wake up before it is done sorting things out, you are inviting trouble for your own mental health.</p>
<p>Therefore, practice going to bed early so you can catch up with a decent 6 to 8 hours of sound sleep.</p>
<p>6. Embrace Life Wholeheartedly<br />
Last but not least, the secret to living a good life is to embrace it wholeheartedly.</p>
<p>Ups and downs are a part of life. If you wait for things to get better in order to feel happier, you might just keep waiting forever.</p>
<p>As Dalai Lama said, ‘happiness is not readymade, it comes from our own actions.’</p>
<p>No matter what your current circumstances might be, reinforce the belief that you can be happy nonetheless. After all, happiness is all about energy.</p>
<p>Stressing over things will only attract more negativity in your life.</p>
<p>Accept the things for what they are, but continue to strive forward.</p>
<p>And if things get too overwhelming, don’t be hesitant to take a step back and relax if needed. Go for an outing with your friends or family or escape to a peaceful place all alone. Research shows that taking breaks, be it a micro or macro level, increases performance by having a positive effect on the person’s thought process.</p>
<p>Avoid over-thinking and stop comparing yourself to others. Everyone is on their own unique journey and you cannot become happy by trying to achieve what they have.</p>
<p>The experience of deep-rooted contentment and positive wellbeing will only come when you start appreciating what you already have.</p>
<p>End Note<br />
Life is only as complicated as we make it be. These tips for living a good life provide easy to implement, road-tested measures that will help you feel happier and more successful.</p>
<p>To sum it up, living a happy and fulfilling life requires that you eat healthier, sleep well, and let go of unproductive habits. Avoid wasting time on social media and do something fruitful such as exercising or meditating. Self-care is the first step towards living a quality life. So, become your own best friend today!</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">390</post-id>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>This May Be The Reason You’re Not Performing How You Want To</title>
		<link>/this-may-be-the-reason-youre-not-performing-how-you-want-to/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[adminilyes1]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 02 Oct 2020 14:10:34 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[LIFE]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/?p=332</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[It doesn’t always come easy, and it most certainly didn’t for me. For at least ten years out of my twenty years being alive, I never even had breakfast in the morning, and at least three out of five meals went incomplete. “What does food have to do with anything?” I’ll be talking a lot [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>It doesn’t always come easy, and it most certainly didn’t for me.</p>
<p>For at least ten years out of my twenty years being alive, I never even had breakfast in the morning, and at least three out of five meals went incomplete.</p>
<figure class="wp-block-pullquote">
<blockquote class="has-text-color has-very-dark-gray-color"><p>“What does food have to do with anything?”</p></blockquote>
</figure>
<p>I’ll be talking a lot more about food and other things throughout this post to help you at least three times your performance rate the moment you leave this page.</p>
<p>For the more significant part of my short life, I slept late and woke up late.</p>
<p>Throughout school, my timeliness broke records for the worst punctuality to have ever been seen by my high school.</p>
<p>My school added fifteen whole minutes to the start of my day because they knew I could not make it on the regular time.</p>
<p>It’s really nothing to be proud of but was definitely hard to refrain from living.</p>
<h3>It’s a constant loop you become trapped in that brings you more than countless disadvantages, and one of the greatest is that your appetite goes right down the gutter.</h3>
<p>Not only do you eat less, <em>you eat worse.</em></p>
<p>Not only do you lose sleep, <em>you waste more time.</em></p>
<p>Not only do you lose joy, <em>you become more angry and unpredictable.</em></p>
<p>Not only do you lose ambition, <em>you develop bad intentions. </em></p>
<p>Appetite is less to do with what you eat,<em> but how you eat. </em></p>
<p>It’s less to do with how you look<em>, but how you feel. </em></p>
<p>See, the right appetite provides you with the energy your body requires and helps you abstain from what is detrimental.</p>
<p>Today, I sleep when I want and wake when I want but automatically these times stay good for my health, and my wealth.</p>
<p>I work a lot less hours than I did during my first 3 years of running a business but get far more done in the few short hours I work.</p>
<p>The happiness and satisfaction I gain from living the life I do makes me a grateful, graceful and extremely enthusiastic individual.</p>
<p>To conclude, the life I live today is the life I envisioned many years ago.</p>
<p>I make changes in my life only to better myself and become better for my environment.</p>
<p>I serve and perform because I love to, never because I have to.</p>
<p>Through lousy habits, you develop a harmful lifestyle, and inevitably this results in negative performance across your entirety.</p>
<p>Let me give you a few pointers on improving your daily performance, spiking your positivity and helping you feel more ecstatic about the life you live.</p>
<p>Please read on to see how I transformed my life, increased my productivity levels massively, spiked up my energy, and how I’m able to feel better about my life each and every day.</p>
<h2><strong>Have Breakfast</strong></h2>
<p>Having breakfast does not mean eating a full-sized meal, it means start your day with some food going down your system. It’s actually not that hard.</p>
<p>I grew my breakfast appetite with one simple trick, and that was having boiling water with freshly squeezed lemon every single morning.</p>
<p>Gradually, my stomach started to open up and my craving for food at breakfast time skyrocketed.</p>
<p>Many times in the week now, I eat more at breakfast time than I do at dinner.</p>
<p>Remember, there is no strict time for breakfast but before 10 AM really hits the spot and beyond this you know you have started your day on the wrong foot.</p>
<h2><strong>Sleep Earlier</strong></h2>
<p>Sleeping earlier does not mean sleeping early. It simply means making a change to your current lifestyle.</p>
<p>If you currently sleep at midnight, for example, bring it an hour back to eleven and execute this sleeping pattern in your life for the next month.</p>
<p>This will cause you to wake up earlier, feel fresher and more energized from the start of the day.</p>
<p>Can you believe that all it takes is one hour of extra sleep in the night and your life will significantly change for the better?</p>
<p>It’s not the sleep that creates impact, it’s the change. Small changes lead to even better outcomes.</p>
<h2><strong>Design Your Life</strong></h2>
<p>Live a life of design, not accident.</p>
<p>You don’t want to wake up in the morning thinking “damn, I did it again.” Instead, you want to feel satisfied with yourself every morning and be able to enter your day with full enthusiasm.</p>
<p>The time you wake up and the time you sleep, the times you eat, the times you play, and the times you work.</p>
<p>All these times are for you to plan and live by.</p>
<p>I will end this point with one straightforward formula of life, the six P’s.</p>
<p>Prior Planning Prevents Piss-Poor Performance.</p>
<p>You plan, you live, and you succeed. Every time a plan is fulfilled, the sense of accomplishment is attained.</p>
<p>For every plan you don’t make, another accident is formed, and a life of error is created.</p>
<h2><strong>Perform Daily</strong></h2>
<p>Act on your goals every day.</p>
<p>As part of your goals should be your desire for change. For every want you have comes its own set of challenges.</p>
<p>These challenges go against your way of living, your integrity, your pride and a lot more internal factors.</p>
<p>It is yourself you must control, take power over and instil change in to experience the greatness of life.</p>
<p>I guess what I mean to say is, whether up or down, sad or ecstatic, you must take some form of action geared for positive change each and every single day.</p>
<p>A day missed is a day wasted, and an effort given is change in fruition.</p>
<p>I have one quote I want you to remember, maybe even take note of somewhere because this will affect your performance tremendously.</p>
<figure class="wp-block-pullquote">
<blockquote class="has-text-color has-very-dark-gray-color"><p>“Imperfect action beats perfect inaction every time.”</p></blockquote>
</figure>
<p>The art of doing nothing only produces negativity, whereas doing something brings you closer to positive change and provides empowerment.</p>
<p>Take full control over your life. This does not stop at your sleep, your diet or your work life but extends over to your thoughts, the information you consume and the relationships you keep.</p>
<p>Living a life of design will provide you with what you need and more.</p>
<p>A life of accident will take from you all the good you have and leave you with dust</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">332</post-id>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>2 Keys to Life and Financial Freedom</title>
		<link>/2-keys-to-life-and-financial-freedom/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[adminilyes1]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 02 Oct 2020 14:01:34 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[LIFE]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/?p=329</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[I have promoted several MLM’s, I have used free traffic to make money, I have used solo ads, I have also sold solo ads, I have tried SEO, I have done webinars, I have spent thousands trying to sell t-shirts, I have attempted e-commerce out on a whole, I have dabbled with PPV marketing with [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>I have promoted several MLM’s, I have used free traffic to make money, I have used solo ads, I have also sold solo ads, I have tried SEO, I have done webinars, I have spent thousands trying to sell t-shirts, I have attempted e-commerce out on a whole, I have dabbled with PPV marketing with CPA offers and every other network which provides traffic, I have tried classified listings, I have bought all sorts of promotions on Fiverr, bloody hell!</p>
<p>The question is, what haven’t I ‘tried’?</p>
<p>I have tried all of these things but could never amount to more than just a small win that changed nothing about my life or the future ahead of me.</p>
<p>Why?</p>
<h3><strong>Focus and consistency.</strong></h3>
<p>The two things I lacked much. I was too busy following trends and wasting what wasn’t my money on things I most definitely did not need.</p>
<p>At this point, I was sure I had the Shiny Object Syndrome.</p>
<p>It got so bad, I was spending thousands of dollars of my partners, and people’s funds that I had leveraged for growth, on high-end coaching programs and courses with no return, all just to try and keep up with what the consumers were consuming right now.</p>
<p><em>A lousy mindset, to say the least.</em></p>
<p>I just wanted to make quick money, I was sold by numbers, screenshots, videos of marketers living the life, marketers flying to people’s houses and getting them paid on the spot.</p>
<p>Ha, the b.s. You come across on the search for success.</p>
<p>We could talk all day about the loop people are stuck in on the hunt for success, but there’s so much shit you get wrapped up in that I could never stop writing about the trials you will face.</p>
<p>I want to save you from this madness because I promise you it’s dangerous, you’ll end up going crazy!</p>
<p>Here’s how I’m going to do that:</p>
<h3>By not selling you a single thing.</h3>
<p>I don’t want your money, and here’s the big reason why…</p>
<p>Because my business does NOT run off my customers/clients, instead, I have personally designed online systems and companies that supply me my income and let me spend more of my time positively impacting my chosen market (that’s one difference I spotted between the genuine and fake marketers).</p>
<p>To get there, it’s simple.</p>
<p>Find something you enjoy, something you can find a genuine mentor in, something that works, something that will sustain for years to come, remove yourself from negative communities, surround yourself with people that support your vision and search for people that will supply you your dreams.</p>
<p>Why am I telling you all of this?</p>
<p>I’ve explained the shit hole I once was in, but I didn’t tell you what happened further, how I changed my entire life around, and hit the majority of my long-term goals within the same year of them being set.</p>
<p>Over the past 5 years, I’ve lost more close friends, family, and money than I could ever imagine I’d lose.</p>
<p>Not talking deaths, but relationships that I had to severe for the betterment of my future.</p>
<p>I’m not only talking seriously wrong investments, like the $18k hole I got myself in but spending countless thousands on mentoring to obtain the information I felt I needed to get closer to my dreams.</p>
<p>Early 2015, I had had enough and decided I’ve gotta start fresh… or throw in the towel.</p>
<p>That same year, an excellent opportunity came my way (any chance was needed at this time due to the struggle I was facing and the holes I found myself in).</p>
<h3><strong>My first freelance client. August 2015.</strong></h3>
<p>This led to my first financial breakthrough in December 2015.</p>
<p>My mentors along the way, including my first freelance client whom all spoke to me the same words I speak to you today.</p>
<p>They all taught me to stay focused and be consistent in whatever I do. These 2 things alone bought me freedom, gave me the life I always desired for myself and the future family I am creating.</p>
<p>Over a quarter of a million dollars was generated through my business in the last 4 months of 2015 and the client I took on went into launch early the following year, they generated over $10,000,000 revenue throughout their first year of being in business.</p>
<p>Remember, slow and steady wins the race</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">329</post-id>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>diffrent ways to create a lasting impressions how to win friends</title>
		<link>/diffrent-ways-to-create-a-lasting-impressions-how-to-win-friends/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[adminilyes1]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 05 Sep 2020 16:46:09 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[LIFE]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/?p=235</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[First impressions are important. What we portray ourselves to be is what gets imprinted in the minds of the people we meet for the first time. It&#8217;s the first few minutes of the conversation they will use to judge you. And the impression you create may last forever. These tips will help you make that [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<hr />
<p>First impressions are important. What we portray ourselves to be is what gets imprinted in the minds of the people we meet for the first time. It&#8217;s the first few minutes of the conversation they will use to judge you. And the impression you create may last forever. These tips will help you make that impression to be great.</p>
<p>1. Make the first move Don&#8217;t wait for people to come to you. Go to them and initiate a conversation. We know how people who are good making friends out of strangers are aggressive. They will approach you and start it like they have known you their whole life. Move up to people and say a &#8216; hi&#8217; to them. The rest will come automatically.</p>
<p>2. Smile A smile is infectious. Smile at a person, and they will smile right back and think you like them, that you want and are happy to be around them. They will, in turn, want to be friends with you. Who doesn&#8217;t like to be around people who like them? There is no nicer way to strike friendship.</p>
<p>3. Maintain eye contact Looking straight into the eyes of someone you are talking to shows you are interested in what they are saying. Avoid looking away or looking at your phone. They may think that they are boring and that you want the conversation to end. Eye contact also makes you appear bold and confident. You will appear honest; dishonest people often avoid eye contact.</p>
<p>4. Listen Always listen when the other person is talking. Avoid unnecessary interruptions, or you may appear rough and belittling. People like it when others allow them the chance to talk.</p>
<p>5 . Radiate warmth Don&#8217;t be dull or the conversation will die away. You will appear bored or uninterested. When talking do it with enthusiasm and look like you are fully immersed in it. Chances ate the other person will copy you, and you will have a great conversation.</p>
<p>6. Complement as a starter A complement is a great conversation starter. Tell them how good they look. Or you. A complement a possession, like how their car looks nice. It works magic, and the other person will open up to conversation.</p>
<p>7. Use proper body language A lazy posture portrays you as uninterested and fidgeting as nervous. Maintaining an upright posture makes you appear confident, and wins you, friends. Using powerful gestures while talking keeps the other person glued to the conversation, and with interest too. Don&#8217;t smile too much or you will appear to lack seriousness. Make it moderate, the kind that shows you are friendly. Avoid pointing at the person you are speaking to; it makes them think you are overly aggressive and domineering.</p>
<p>8. Have a sense of humor No one wants to hang around a boring person. A laugh makes for a great conversation. Crack a joke or two and laugh together. The person will never forget you. People like to be around people who are funny. It makes life less serious and interesting. To be a great cracker of jokes, make people who are talented in humor your friends. You will learn the art from them with time. Or you can watch comedy and learn some punch lines.</p>
<p>9. Create a personality to fit We all behave differently when talking to different people. Like for example, the way you would talk to a musician is not the same way you would talk to a company executive. And for a reason, because we view life differently depending on our professions. So create a personality that blends with theirs. This way you will avoid offending them, or appearing irrelevant and uninteresting. You can start off your conversation by knowing what they do so you can adjust your conversation accordingly. Using these tips will help you win friend and create a lasting impression on the people you meet in your daily life.</p>
<p>10. Find out what you have in common Start by talking about something that interests you. Or you can ask them what they do, or what their hobbies are. Once you get talking about something you both love, there will be no stopping to the conversation. And you will form a strong friendship based on shared likes. You can even tell them where you live or work. If you share a neighborhood or company, you will instantly become friends with a lot to talk about.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">235</post-id>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>these 10 exercises will rock your body</title>
		<link>/these-10-exercises-will-rock-your-body/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[adminilyes1]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 24 Aug 2020 10:10:25 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[LIFE]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/?p=136</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[In today&#8217;s world, you don&#8217;t need to go to a gym to get a full workout. You can do it from the comfort of your home. Here are some examples of things you can do. You probably don&#8217;t want to do everything in a single workout, however, make sure you rotate so that your whole [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>In today&#8217;s world, you don&#8217;t need to go to a gym to get a full workout. You can do it from the comfort of your home. Here are some examples of things you can do. You probably don&#8217;t want to do everything in a single workout, however, make sure you rotate so that your whole body is getting worked at some point. Today, we will discuss our top 10 favorites with no equipment exercises which you should include in your own home workouts.</p>



<p>This old military favorite is a tried and true winner and muscle builder. It&#8217;s easy to perform and just about everyone knows how to do it. I won&#8217;t go into detail explaining how to do a push-up but, I will give you some important tips. Begin by doing as many push-ups as you can do &#8212; until you can&#8217;t do anymore. Then rest for one to two minutes. Then begin again doing push-ups until you can&#8217;t do anymore. Rest again for one to two minutes and continue doing this sequence for a total of three times or three sets.</p>



<p class="has-vivid-cyan-blue-color has-text-color">2. Pull-Ups Or Chin-Ups</p>



<p class="has-vivid-cyan-blue-color has-text-color"> </p>



<p>Again another standby exercise that most people know how to do. The point here is to not stress your neck. Anchor your legs to a chair or table so that they will not lift up as you do the movement. Bend your knees to a &#8212; 90 angle (this will not be a full situp, but a partial crunch.) By now you should know the routine perform as many as you can &#8212; for a total of three sets &#8212; resting no more than one to two minutes between sets.</p>



<p class="has-vivid-cyan-blue-color has-text-color">4. Abs crunches</p>



<p class="has-vivid-cyan-blue-color has-text-color"> </p>



<p>Press up is an excellent exercise for your upper body and back muscles and that too without the help of any equipment. Start by keeping your knees and hips in a line and keep your hands apart wider than your shoulder width. Make this exercise hard by placing your feet on a bench and make it easier by putting your hands on a higher place.</p>



<p class="has-vivid-cyan-blue-color has-text-color">6. Step-up</p>



<p>This exercise can be easily performed at your home or at a park. You just need a bench for this. Place your heel on the bench and then step up. Step down with less slowly. Make this exercise harder by stepping on to a higher object or pushing less hard from the ground. If you find this exercise hard the step onto a lower bench or push harder from the ground.</p>



<p class="has-vivid-cyan-blue-color has-text-color">7. Salt bridge</p>



<p>This is a good exercise for muscles on the sides of your torso. Li on your one side with your elbows and feet in a straight line. Now elevate your hips. This position strengthens your torso muscles. Make it easier by using a bench to raise your hand or elbow.</p>



<p class="has-vivid-cyan-blue-color has-text-color">8. Bodyweight squats</p>



<p>No weight, nothing. Just you squatting with your own body weight. Many people think that because this is a simple exercise that it&#8217;s automatically easy. Not so. This really tests you. What you ideally want to do is 25 squats in a row. Then take a short rest and repeat. Doing this for 4 sets every day not only will tone and tighten your legs, but also help you to shed fat from all over your body.</p>



<p>It is only in shadow boxing that one can imagine the opponent having attacking and defending moves played out through the rounds. Where counteractions can be practiced without an actual opponent striking or even the threat of being hut-like when in sparring, (sparring meaning: in the ring against an opponent in the boxing gym ring, usually a club mate).</p>



<p>There is a hesitancy following through all actions effectively to the point of mastery, if under threat of being punched in the face every time if throwing incorrectly.     This undermines the potential at hand by not completing actual punch moves or stance positioning correctly. When shadow boxing there is no threat existing, having no opponent. Which then removes the &#8216; being hut factor &#8216; drawback so important ring movement abilities and punching effectiveness are able to have mastery at any level.</p>



<p class="has-vivid-cyan-blue-color has-text-color"> </p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">136</post-id>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>being in love can boost your health and make you look great</title>
		<link>/being-in-love-can-boost-your-health-and-make-you-look-great/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[adminilyes1]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 23 Aug 2020 22:58:34 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[LIFE]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/?p=123</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Besides a heart full of love, those little shivers and a big smile, being in a relationship can bring some positive health benefits. It can improve the physical, emotional and mental well-being of both parties in the relationship. This being said, not all relationships tend to realize these benefits; it only works for stable well-cultivated [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Besides a heart full of love, those little shivers and a big smile, being in a relationship can bring some positive health benefits. It can improve the physical, emotional and mental well-being of both parties in the relationship. This being said, not all relationships tend to realize these benefits; it only works for stable well-cultivated relationships.</p>
<p>Physical benefits of love<br />
Being in love bring a sparkle in your eyes and make your eyes look brighter. Research proves that people who are in love tend to experience more frequent adrenaline rushes due to physical and emotional arousal. Adrenaline and sex hormones are responsible for feelings of love. They make your eyes dilate giving you a dramatic doe-eyed look which most people find attractive.</p>
<p>A healthy love relationship with great sex can improve lip health. The rushes that people get when they are in love or when they feel in love improve blood flow in the lips giving them a plumper, healthier look. It makes your pout look a bit plumper which looks good.</p>
<p>Having regular sex improves the amount of blood that flows through the breasts in women giving them a firm look. It also increases the levels of oxytocin which help to keep breasts cancer free.</p>
<p>Research shows that engaging in regular sex increase hair growth. Sex leads to increase in the production of hormones like testosterone which help to decrease hair loss and boost hair growth. It also makes your hair shine. Hair loss can also be as a result of stress. Stress activates neurotransmitters that interfere with hair growth. It also causes blood capillaries to constrict which results in poor blood flow to the scalp hence reducing hair growth. A happy relationship offers a platform for sharing which helps to reduce stress hence curbing hair loss.</p>
<p>A stable relationship is the beginning of a long, healthy life. Studies carried out since the late 70s show that people in happy long-term relationships are generally healthier than those who aren’t. They tend to have a lower risk of suffering from stress-related diseases like ulcer and high blood pressure. They also have lower cancer rates too.</p>
<p>Mental and emotional benefits of love<br />
Being in a relationship determines your levels of energy, both physical and emotional. While being in sad relationship drains your mental energy, being in a happy relationship helps build positive energy. A stable relationship that offers happiness offers makes you feel cherished and loved hence making you feel good about yourself.</p>
<p>A relationship works in a give-and-take mechanism. It puts you in a position to where you can give and receive at the same time. Research shows that giving lights up the midbrain region of your brain which is responsible for pleasure. Giving derives a similar pleasure to that of sex which makes you happier.</p>
<p>A healthy relationship promotes internal growth. It allows you to learn and grow with a person either directly or indirectly. A loving partner will always make sure that you are the best version of yourself. They will urge you to explore different versions of you and find your best self. A more mature partner can help mentor and direct the other partner as they grow in love. A relationship offers a mirror to you: it allows you to look at yourself in the mirror of another person. Broken relationships also offer lessons on places one might have gone wrong and need to improve. A relationship allows two people to grow individually as well as grow one another.</p>
<p>There are many things that could stress someone: work, family, responsibilities, failures, and friends. Being in a relationship allows some to share their mental burden. The other party may or may not be able to help, but a keen ear from a loving partner makes you feel good. Being sure that you have someone to talk to and work things out together helps you handle stress in a better way. Having less stress promotes good mental and physical health.</p>
<p>In conclusion, there are a number of benefits that come from a stable relationship. All it takes is two willing people to sit down and work together to build a happy relationship and both parties could lead a happy, healthy physical and mental life.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">123</post-id>	</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
