<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	
	xmlns:georss="http://www.georss.org/georss"
	xmlns:geo="http://www.w3.org/2003/01/geo/wgs84_pos#"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Inspire &#8211; Dailytweet</title>
	<atom:link href="/category/inspire/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>/</link>
	<description></description>
	<lastBuildDate>Wed, 09 Dec 2020 16:46:19 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=5.6</generator>

<image>
	<url>/wp-content/uploads/2020/12/cropped-android-chrome-512x512-1-1-32x32.png</url>
	<title>Inspire &#8211; Dailytweet</title>
	<link>/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
<site xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">185396299</site>	<item>
		<title>Achieve Excellence in Life by Committing to These 7 Daily Habits</title>
		<link>/achieve-excellence-in-life-by-committing-to-these-7-daily-habits/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[adminilyes1]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 24 Nov 2020 08:16:16 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Inspire]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/?p=438</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Tips to achieve excellence in lifeWho doesn’t want to live a happier, more fulfilling life? Obviously, everyone wants to achieve excellence in life. We try to pursue excellence throughout our lives, yet very few of us come close to achieving it. Whether you are trying to strengthen the relationships with your loved ones, eat healthier, [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>Tips to achieve excellence in life<br>Who doesn’t want to live a happier, more fulfilling life? Obviously, everyone wants to achieve excellence in life.</p>



<p>We try to pursue excellence throughout our lives, yet very few of us come close to achieving it.</p>



<p>Whether you are trying to strengthen the relationships with your loved ones, eat healthier, perform better at work, or simply improve the overall quality of your life in general, you are likely to find yourself stumbling time and again.</p>



<p>It sure is difficult to achieve excellence in life. But it certainly isn’t impossible.</p>



<p>1. Wake Up Early in the Morning</p>



<p>If you really want to be successful in life, then you must start your day earlier than usual. And by waking up early, we don’t mean getting up just in time to have a proper breakfast and dress properly without having to hop around while putting on your jeans.</p>



<p>You need to practice rising with the sun – quite literally!</p>



<p>Why?</p>



<p>Well, because there’s something sacred about the pre-dawn hours. There are utmost peace and tranquility in the environment, the world is asleep, and there are no distractions to take away your focus.</p>



<p>Use this time to nourish your mind, body, and soul.</p>



<p>Practice yoga, do some exercise or read some quality books to relax and unwind. Alternatively, you can also use the early morning hours to get through the toughest tasks of the day.</p>



<p>2. Drink Plenty of Water</p>



<p>When it comes to staying alert and energized, nothing works wonders like drinking sufficient water throughout the day.</p>



<p>Give the fact that 70% of the human body is comprised of H2O, it should not come as a surprise why drinking plenty of water refreshes you all over.</p>



<p>Instead of gulping down coffee the first thing in the morning, make it a habit to drink a glass of water on an empty stomach instead. Not only does it provide numerous health benefits, but it also rejuvenates you instantly, giving you the mental sharpness you need to kickstart your day.</p>



<p>3. Practice Mindfulness</p>



<p>Since prehistoric times, meditation has been hailed for its effectiveness in helping people achieve excellence in life. It rewires your brain, develops concentration, and is a great way to go about fighting daily stressors.</p>



<p>Meditating for as little as ten minutes every day can train your mind to focus on any given subject. This facilitates you in meeting the daily agenda and ultimately achieving your life goals at large.</p>



<p>It makes you more aware of yourself as well as your surroundings and helps you develop positive thoughts. Moreover, meditation is also known to enhance mood and correct the sleep-wake cycle.</p>



<p>According to research, meditation is known to increase employee productivity by 120%.</p>



<p>4. Write Everything Down</p>



<p>Whether it’s the to-do list or a list of ideas for your next project, get it down on paper.</p>



<p>We are living in the age of digitalization, where even the simplest of tasks such as opening a door is fully automated. But don’t be surprised when we tell you to jot things down using an actual pen and paper.</p>



<p>Paste the paper on your refrigerator door, by your office desk, or any other place where you will notice it at least a couple of times throughout the day. When you see the list of tasks that are still pending, you will be more conscious about utilizing your time in the best possible manner so as to get things done in time.</p>



<p>Similarly, you can add to your list of creative ideas so that you have everything in one place when it’s time to work on the project.</p>



<p>Based on various studies conducted by renowned universities like Harvard, Yale, and Stanford University, maintaining a gratitude journal creates greater enthusiasm, strengthens determination and even improves your immune system.</p>



<p>5. Get a Daily Dose of Inspiration</p>



<p>Never ever underestimate the power of positive reinforcement when it comes to being more successful in life. But you don’t necessarily have to rely on others to acknowledge your efforts and praise you for your work.</p>



<p>Be your own cheerleader.</p>



<p>Remind yourself of your true potential every day, and believe that you have already had the power to turn your dreams into a reality. You just need to learn how to channel it in the right direction.</p>



<p>Whether it looks silly doing so or not, look yourself in the mirror and say it out loud, ‘I can do it.’</p>



<p>Another great way to achieve excellence in life is by developing a positive mindset is to learn from the experience of people who have attained the same.</p>



<p>Read the biographies of successful CEOs and iconic leaders to gain inspiration from the legends</p>



<p>6. Actively Remove Distractions</p>



<p>Distractions deter you from making significant progress on the road to success. And it goes without saying that your smartphone is perhaps the biggest distraction out there.</p>



<p>Survey results show that an average employee spends more than two hours on social media at work every day. This accounts for a loss of 13% of their total productivity.</p>



<p>Make sure to keep your smartphone on silent mode when working so that the frequent notifications don’t distract you from the task at hand. What’s even better is to stay logged out of your social media accounts on your mobile phone so that you aren’t tempted to check your feed every few minutes.</p>



<p>7. Set Priorities</p>



<p>Priority #1 circled with red pencil<br>You can be moving all your life and still not get anywhere.</p>



<p>If you value petty tasks over the more important ones, chances are you will always be stuck in a rut.</p>



<p>Most people try to get small things done first so that they can give their undivided attention to the main task later on. If you follow a similar approach, it’s best to stop doing so now.</p>



<p>More often than not, the trivial chores end up taking longer than expected. Plus, they drain your energy, so you lose focus on the real deal.</p>



<p>Learn to prioritize, and don’t be hesitant to delegate when required.</p>



<p>EndNote<br>The bottom line is that if you want to accomplish your goals and achieve excellence in life, you must first set straight your daily schedule. Building healthy habits automatically enable you to attain a productive lifestyle and live the life you have always wanted</p>



<p></p>


<p>&nbsp;</p>]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">438</post-id>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Why Studying Personal Development Can Slow Down Your Growth</title>
		<link>/why-studying-personal-development-can-slow-down-your-growth/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[adminilyes1]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 24 Nov 2020 07:46:24 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Inspire]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/?p=433</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[If you have decided to take control of your life and actively work towards becoming a better version of yourself, congratulations are in order. You have surely made a good decision and we commend you for that. Studying personal development can help you overcome your fears, push past boundaries, and gradually work your way towards [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>If you have decided to take control of your life and actively work towards becoming a better version of yourself, congratulations are in order.</p>



<p>You have surely made a good decision and we commend you for that.</p>



<p>Studying personal development can help you overcome your fears, push past boundaries, and gradually work your way towards the fulfillment of your dreams.</p>



<p>But coming from someone with years of experience in the field of self-development, believe us when we say that there are many disadvantages of studying personal development too.</p>



<p>No, we don’t mean to discourage you. And we definitely don’t want you to think that the ability to achieve excellence in life lies beyond your control. &nbsp;&nbsp;</p>



<p>All we are saying is that there are certain drawbacks of studying personal development that only a few people are aware of. And usually, these are the people who eagerly started out on the path to self-development, only to come to a standstill as negative feelings like low self-esteem begin to take over.</p>



<p>If you want to make the most of studying personal development and get the results that you desire, it’s essential to know what you are signing up for.</p>



<p>Here, we explore the dark side of personal development programs that hardly anyone ever talks about.</p>



<h2>The Disadvantages of Studying Personal Development</h2>



<figure class="wp-block-image"><img src="https://web.archive.org/web/20200804030926im_/https://347077-1073788-1-raikfcquaxqncofqfm.stackpathdns.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/02/self-development-study-1024x575.jpeg" alt="" class="wp-image-359"/><figcaption>personal development concept on blackboard</figcaption></figure>



<p>The biggest problem with studying personal development stems from the fact that the way it is taken up often subverts the very benefit that people want to get out of it.</p>



<p>It doesn’t matter whether you are planning to pursue self-improvement by reading self-help books, watching online tutorials, attending a workshop, or by hiring a coach – because most self-help programs take a manipulative approach to encourage users to take charge of their lives.</p>



<p>They somehow end up making you feel as if there is something ‘wrong’ about you.</p>



<p>Sure, you might have some bad habits, such as procrastinating, that you yourself know need to be rectified. But there’s a high chance that in the drive to be more productive and live a more fulfilling life, you will develop an obsession towards perfectionism.</p>



<p>You start comparing your success and failures to others and gradually set unrealistic expectations for your own self. When you are highly focused on improving yourself, it’s only natural to think that you aren’t good enough at the moment.</p>



<p>As a result, you might sink into low self-esteem. Your self-confidence takes a toll as a feeling of inadequacy takes over and you accept this self-formed notion that you fall into a group of individuals who need to be ‘fixed.’</p>



<p>And it is this very belief that you need to need to undergo an exemplary change to achieve more in life is what proves detrimental to your growth.</p>



<h2>Why Studying Personal Development Can Slow Down Your Growth</h2>



<p>Let’s take a more in-depth look at why and how studying personal development has the potential to backfire and lead to results that are exactly the opposite of what you set out to achieve in the first place.</p>



<h3>It Encourages You to Pursue Unrealistic Goals</h3>



<figure class="wp-block-image"><img src="https://web.archive.org/web/20200804030926im_/https://347077-1073788-1-raikfcquaxqncofqfm.stackpathdns.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/02/encourgaes-to-pursue-unrealistic-goals-1024x576.jpg" alt="" class="wp-image-360"/></figure>



<p>It’s no secret that defining your goals in life is the prerequisite of attaining excellence. But what if you start setting absurd goals? Or worse, what if others start defining the goals for you?</p>



<p>Of course, a professional personal development coach will help you discover your main purpose in life and then help you effectively work towards attaining it. But with self-help gurus available a dime a dozen in the online world, it shouldn’t be too surprising why many people willing to improve themselves end up trying to please others instead.</p>



<h3>It Traps You into Things That Aren’t Working</h3>



<p>Identifying the hurdles on your road to success is a vital part of all personal development programs. But there’s a catch to this step.</p>



<p>While the purpose of recognizing the roadblocks is to come with the best measures for navigating your way around them, most people become so intent on the first part that they forget to take the next step.</p>



<p>Put simply, one of the main disadvantages of studying personal development is that you can get too preoccupied with the challenges in life. You constantly zero in on things that didn’t go according to plan. Consequently, you see your life as far less than perfect and become more prone to feeling unhappy and unsuccessful.</p>



<h2>How to Make Personal Development Work For You</h2>



<figure class="wp-block-image"><img src="https://web.archive.org/web/20200804030926im_/https://347077-1073788-1-raikfcquaxqncofqfm.stackpathdns.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/02/how-to-make-it-work-for-you.jpg" alt="" class="wp-image-361"/></figure>



<p>If you want to gain the fruitful results of studying personal development that others often rave about, it’s important to learn this one basic thing: the negative things in life will scream at you, demanding attention, but the positive things only whisper. You need to seek them out yourself and excellence will soon follow on its own.</p>



<p>Study personal development with an open mindset.</p>



<p>Rather than being discouraged and viewing yourself as an individual who’s full of faults, understand that no one, and I repeat,&nbsp;<em>no one&nbsp;</em>is perfect.</p>



<p>Perfectionism is simply an illusion that will destroy your peace of mind the more you run after it. Your journey is yours alone. So, instead of seeing other people’s success as milestones, use their achievements to gain inspiration and continue moving forward on the road to betterment.</p>



<p>Above all, keep in mind that much like achieving happiness, personal development is not about arriving at a station – it’s the journey itself that counts.</p>



<p>You won’t magically wake up one day as the best version of yourself. The little steps you take towards improvement are all that matter at the end.</p>



<h2>End Note</h2>



<p>If you look up the term ‘studying personal development’ on the internet, you will be presented with a long list of all the benefits it brings and why it is a crucial step for anyone who’s willing to live a happier and more successful life. Hopefully, this article will have given you a fair idea of the disadvantages of studying personal development and why it’s important to prepare yourself well mentally before pursuing the path of self-development.</p>



<p></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">433</post-id>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Why Self Esteem Is The REAL Key To Success</title>
		<link>/why-self-esteem-is-the-real-key-to-success/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[adminilyes1]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 02 Oct 2020 14:43:30 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Inspire]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/?p=342</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[What is self-admiration? Is it the hidden key to success? And what does admiring your own self mean anyway? Find out the answers in this detailed guide discussing the ultimate secret to achieving more in life. If you ask people what the secret is for living a successful life, you will come across a variety [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><em>What is self-admiration? Is it the hidden key to success? And what does admiring your own self mean anyway? Find out the answers in this detailed guide discussing the ultimate secret to achieving more in life.</em></p>
<p>If you ask people what the secret is for living a successful life, you will come across a variety of answers such as identifying your goals, pursuing your passion, developing a plan of action, being consistent in your efforts, perseverance, and so on.</p>
<p>But if you ask <em>successful</em> people what enabled them to reach where they are and live the life they had always envisioned, you are likely to find most of them answering something along the lines of ‘believing in yourself’ and ‘being confident in your abilities.’</p>
<h2>Finding the Hidden Key to Success</h2>
<figure class="wp-block-image size-large"><img class="wp-image-353" src="https://web.archive.org/web/20200804023617im_/https://347077-1073788-1-raikfcquaxqncofqfm.stackpathdns.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/02/self-development-tips-1024x628.jpg" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" srcset="//web.archive.org/web/20200804023617im_/https://347077-1073788-1-raikfcquaxqncofqfm.stackpathdns.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/02/self-development-tips-1024x628.jpg 1024w, //web.archive.org/web/20200804023617im_/https://347077-1073788-1-raikfcquaxqncofqfm.stackpathdns.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/02/self-development-tips-300x184.jpg 300w, //web.archive.org/web/20200804023617im_/https://347077-1073788-1-raikfcquaxqncofqfm.stackpathdns.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/02/self-development-tips-768x471.jpg 768w, //web.archive.org/web/20200804023617im_/https://347077-1073788-1-raikfcquaxqncofqfm.stackpathdns.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/02/self-development-tips-1080x662.jpg 1080w, //web.archive.org/web/20200804023617im_/https://347077-1073788-1-raikfcquaxqncofqfm.stackpathdns.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/02/self-development-tips.jpg 1280w" alt="" /></figure>
<p>Take a hint from the success stories of famous personalities like Oprah Winfrey and J.K. Rowling. Despite being born into a low-income family, Winfrey is known by millions of people all over the world today as a ‘billionaire philanthropist.’ Rowling, at one point in her life, was living penny-to-penny, and now, she is one of the wealthiest people in the world.</p>
<p>What did they have in common that made them so wildly successful?</p>
<p>They didn’t give up on their dreams!</p>
<p>They believed that they could turn their lives around and have whatever their hearts desired. And that’s precisely what they did!</p>
<p>Self-confidence. That’s where they started.</p>
<p>And it all begins with developing a sense of self-admiration – i.e., believing that you have the power to change your life regardless of what your current circumstances might be forcing you to think otherwise.</p>
<p>Whether you are on the road to self-improvement, trying to find the hidden key to success, or wondering if a lack of confidence affects your quality of life, this post is for you.</p>
<p>In this guide to life freedom, we discuss the following aspects of self-admiration:</p>
<ul>
<li>What is self-admiration?</li>
<li>What are the benefits of self-admiration?</li>
<li>How to gain freedom in life through self-admiration?</li>
</ul>
<p>Ready to turn your dreams into a reality and live the life you have always wanted?</p>
<p>Let’s begin by taking a more in-depth look at what self-admiration is and shattering some commonly held but false beliefs about this feeling of self-love.</p>
<h2>What Is Self Admiration?</h2>
<p>Well, in the simplest terms, self-admiration is just what you would generally understand by the individual words that it is comprised of –admiring yourself.</p>
<p>Self-admiration is the feeling of being pleased with yourself. It is thinking well of yourself and taking pride in who you are.</p>
<p>However, the concept of self-admiration can be quite confusing at times. This is because the term ‘self-admiration’ tends to mislead people into viewing the idea under a negative light.</p>
<h3>Self Admiration – What It Is NOT</h3>
<p>Being fond of oneself is usually notorious for leading to disastrous results. This is because self-admiration is generally considered to be synonymous with conceitedness, self-centeredness, egocentrism, and arrogance.</p>
<p>While a thesaurus might approve of this notion, keep in mind that, in reality, self-admiration is NOT the same as any of these ideas.</p>
<p>Some scholars have written books about how self-admiration is a ‘disease of the soul’ as it is responsible for leading people into sin. They believe that self-admiration tricks you into a false sense of self-righteousness. It deludes you into thinking that you are perfect. So, you stop striving towards betterment and ultimately fall into a stagnant lifestyle.</p>
<p>It would be incorrect to say that they are entirely wrong in their stance – because if practiced at extremely high levels, self-admiration can indeed lead to such results.</p>
<p>However, self-admiration, in essence, is not a bad thing. Basically, there is a very thin line that distinguishes self-admiration from other harmful behaviors like self-obsession, self-absorption, self-centeredness, and selfishness itself.</p>
<p>It is essential to understand this if you want to be more successful in life.</p>
<h3>So, What Does Admiring Yourself Really Mean?</h3>
<figure class="wp-block-image size-large"><img class="wp-image-354" src="https://web.archive.org/web/20200804023617im_/https://347077-1073788-1-raikfcquaxqncofqfm.stackpathdns.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/02/what-does-self-admiration-means-1024x682.jpg" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" srcset="//web.archive.org/web/20200804023617im_/https://347077-1073788-1-raikfcquaxqncofqfm.stackpathdns.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/02/what-does-self-admiration-means-1024x682.jpg 1024w, //web.archive.org/web/20200804023617im_/https://347077-1073788-1-raikfcquaxqncofqfm.stackpathdns.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/02/what-does-self-admiration-means-300x200.jpg 300w, //web.archive.org/web/20200804023617im_/https://347077-1073788-1-raikfcquaxqncofqfm.stackpathdns.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/02/what-does-self-admiration-means-768x512.jpg 768w, //web.archive.org/web/20200804023617im_/https://347077-1073788-1-raikfcquaxqncofqfm.stackpathdns.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/02/what-does-self-admiration-means-1080x720.jpg 1080w, //web.archive.org/web/20200804023617im_/https://347077-1073788-1-raikfcquaxqncofqfm.stackpathdns.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/02/what-does-self-admiration-means.jpg 1280w" alt="" /></figure>
<p>Self-admiration is linked with building self-esteem. It is about celebrating your individuality, or in simple words, feeling <em>confident</em> in your own skin.</p>
<p>It is the belief that you are not just worthy of receiving good things in life, but more so, that you are perfectly capable of achieving them on your own – if you want.</p>
<p>Self-admiration is what empowers you to attain excellence. It motivates you to strive towards your goals in a way that you are bound to be successful in your endeavors.</p>
<p>Admiring yourself has nothing to do with good looks. Rather, it entails embracing yourself wholeheartedly – imperfections and all.</p>
<p>Self-admiration means that you appreciate your uniqueness and what makes you, you.</p>
<h2>Why Self-Admiration Is the Hidden Key to Success – The Benefits of Being Your Own Admirer</h2>
<p>Everyone feels proud of themselves whenever they are successful in attaining what they had set out to achieve. Self-admiration means that you take pride in the so-called ‘failures’ as well.</p>
<p>When you stop being too hard on yourself and realize that mistakes ultimately help you improve, you are able to push past your fear of failure and work towards your goals, feeling more confident in your skills. This further increases your chances of success.</p>
<p>There are many reasons why self-admiration is the hidden key to success:</p>
<ul>
<li>It makes you optimistic about the future</li>
<li>It helps you put in your best efforts as you realize that you have the ability to accomplish your goals</li>
<li>Self-admiration encourages you to treat yourself kindly</li>
<li>It motivates you to take better care of yourself. Nurturing self-love is important as it helps you eat healthier and stay in good shape by maintaining an active lifestyle</li>
<li>Admiring yourself and your achievements in life so far automatically uplift your mood and make you feel energized. This, in turn, increases your overall satisfaction in life</li>
<li>Self-admiration helps you break free from unproductive habits such as procrastinating by motivating you to get things done on time</li>
<li>It enables you to maintain a positive outlook on life even if things seem pretty bleak. This is crucial for living that’s full of joy always and not dictated by factors that were out of your control anyway</li>
<li>It makes you more grateful by instilling a sense of appreciation for everything in life – even the apparently bad ones</li>
<li>Self-admiration strengthens your relationships with others</li>
<li>It builds your interpersonal skills as others feel attracted to your amiable personality</li>
</ul>
<h2>How to Gain Freedom in Life – Self-Admiration Made Easy</h2>
<p>Still not sure how self-admiration can help you navigate your way on the road to success? Or did you get the idea but are confused about implementing it in the right manner to get the desired results?</p>
<p>Whatever the case might be, carefully read through the following steps to develop a deeper insight into how appreciating and believing in yourself can take you to greater heights.</p>
<h3>Be True to Yourself</h3>
<p>An important step in learning to be comfortable in your own skin is to stop pretending and doing things for the sake of making others happy.</p>
<p>More often than not, living a happier, more purposeful life is not that difficult, but we tend to complicate things for ourselves. Trying to please others might help you win the love of your life or appear ‘good’ in the eyes of others temporarily. However, the relationships you form on that basis are bound to be hollow, and so, will fail to withstand the test of time.</p>
<p>Being more successful is all about growing and evolving into the person you are capable of being. And you cannot reach there by trying to be like someone else.</p>
<p>As Oscar Wilde famously said, ‘Be yourself, because everyone else is already taken.’</p>
<p>Plus, an original is always worth more than a copy.</p>
<p>When you start appreciating your own worth, the world naturally follows suit.</p>
<h3>Let It Go</h3>
<figure class="wp-block-image size-large"><img class="wp-image-355" src="https://web.archive.org/web/20200804023617im_/https://347077-1073788-1-raikfcquaxqncofqfm.stackpathdns.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/02/let-it-go-1024x614.jpg" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" srcset="//web.archive.org/web/20200804023617im_/https://347077-1073788-1-raikfcquaxqncofqfm.stackpathdns.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/02/let-it-go-1024x614.jpg 1024w, //web.archive.org/web/20200804023617im_/https://347077-1073788-1-raikfcquaxqncofqfm.stackpathdns.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/02/let-it-go-300x180.jpg 300w, //web.archive.org/web/20200804023617im_/https://347077-1073788-1-raikfcquaxqncofqfm.stackpathdns.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/02/let-it-go-768x460.jpg 768w, //web.archive.org/web/20200804023617im_/https://347077-1073788-1-raikfcquaxqncofqfm.stackpathdns.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/02/let-it-go-1080x647.jpg 1080w, //web.archive.org/web/20200804023617im_/https://347077-1073788-1-raikfcquaxqncofqfm.stackpathdns.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/02/let-it-go-627x376.jpg 627w, //web.archive.org/web/20200804023617im_/https://347077-1073788-1-raikfcquaxqncofqfm.stackpathdns.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/02/let-it-go-440x264.jpg 440w, //web.archive.org/web/20200804023617im_/https://347077-1073788-1-raikfcquaxqncofqfm.stackpathdns.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/02/let-it-go.jpg 1280w" alt="" /></figure>
<p>One of the best ways to leverage the power of self-admiration for being more successful in life is to identify and deal with the root causes of low self-esteem.</p>
<p>Perhaps you have always been the target of criticism from your family members. Maybe your parents’ style of upbringing led you into believing that you aren’t ‘good enough.’ Or perhaps you used to be a confident person until you stepped into the corporate world and had to deal with a lot of complaints from your manager or your clients.</p>
<p>No matter what the main reason might be, you need to raise your self-esteem back up again.</p>
<p>Remind yourself that what others think of you is none of your business. No one can make you feel inferior without your consent. Harsh remarks and rude comments cannot cause you any harm until you give them the power to.</p>
<p>And if it’s about your job performance, or if it’s truly constructive criticism, take the feedback with an open mind. Try to see things from the other person’s perspective. This helps make critical work for you.</p>
<h3>Get Things Done</h3>
<p>Maybe you want to start your own business, buy a big house, or establish a school for the underprivileged children, and so on. If your own goal seems to be too far from reality, there’s no need to be disheartened. Rather than feeling overwhelmed by the big picture, focus on taking small steps instead.</p>
<p>While others can surely support you in your mission, it is important to realize that the power to accomplish that goal lies with you only.</p>
<p>Break down bigger tasks into smaller, actionable steps. When you are able to complete the initial steps successfully, you will feel more confident in your abilities. It then provides a strong point for growing your self-belief even further.</p>
<h2>Disclaimer: Self Admiration is Healthy, Narcissism Is Not</h2>
<p>When you hear the word ‘self-admiration,’ do you picture a person looking at themselves in a mirror admiringly?</p>
<p>If you answered yes, you are not alone. And you are also not right.</p>
<p>This type of self-love is tilted more towards what is commonly known as narcissism.</p>
<p>Becoming your own admirer doesn’t mean that you spend hours gazing at your reflection each day. Nor does it mean that looking at your own image should be a source of utmost delight.</p>
<p>Of course, acknowledging that you are no less than an awesome person is part of the idea, but that surely isn’t what self-admiration is all about.</p>
<p>Self-admiration focuses on utilizing your inner strengths rather than your physical goodness to unlock the door to new opportunities. Narcissism, on the other hand, means that you are more concerned with the way you look rather than how well you perform. In a way, it makes you more dependent on others because you become reliant on external validation to work harder.</p>
<p>However, self-admiration lets you internalize a sense of worthiness. So, whether or not you get the praise you deserve, you always feel good about yourself anyway.</p>
<p>Put simply, self-admiration is healthy; narcissism is not. Period!</p>
<h2>End Note</h2>
<p>In the words of Prem Pal Rawat, ‘When there can be that admiration for the self, the rest is very, very simple.’</p>
<p>Rawat is an Indian American who earned the Global Peace Ambassador award for his works promoting human welfare through self-knowledge and self-improvement.</p>
<p>This alone is a solid proof that self-admiration is indeed the hidden key to success.</p>
<p>Self-admiration helps you realize your inner talents, making you feel more confident in pursuing your goals in a way that yields the desired results.</p>
<p>Just keep in mind that self-obsession and self-admiration are not the different sides of the same coin – the two are completely poles apart. The former will deter you from the road to success by making you arrogant and conceited, whereas the latter will allow you to effectively work towards bringing a change for good. So, start being your own cheerleader and witness how it empowers you to bring your A-game!</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">342</post-id>	</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
